

Reliable and enthusiastic general laborer with a degree in construction management. Skilled in landscaping for commercial and residential sites. Trained and certified in cement finishing, with an eye towards becoming a master finisher within the next two years. Organized and timely with the ability to complete jobs on time and to spec.

Professional Experience

Construction General Laborer

Colorado Construction Associates, Boulder, CO May 2016 - Present

- · Execute a variety of concrete work, including cutting and grouting
- · Load and unload construction material and supply deliveries
- Manage and maintain assigned hand and power tools
- Complete miscellaneous duties as instructed by the site supervisor

Landscaping General Laborer

CM Staffing Company, Boulder, CO October 2014 - May 2016

- · Mowed lawns, trimmed hedges, and raked leaves
- Managed and maintained landscapes and gardens, including planting, pruning, removing debris, and other tasks
- Installed concrete stepping-stones and statues
- Assembled decorative structures, such as gazebos, benches, and canopies

19 Brookhaven Way, Boulder. CO 80300 Li\$aBerman@email,net (720) 987-6543

Education

Associate in Applied Science in Construction Management

Boulder Community College, Boulder, CO June 2011 - August 2014

Key Skills

- Landscaping skills, including moving and planting
- OSHA trained
- Ability to use hand and power tools
- Trained to use Aerial Lift machine
- Ability to lift Over 75lb\$

Certifications

- Concrete Flatwork Finisher
 Certification
 - Residential Concrete Foundation
 Technician Certification